https://www.ubifcu.com/privacy-policy

Notary Public Services
Share Draft (Checking)
Account Withdrawal
ACH Improper Entry (PDF)
ACH Origination (PDF)
ACH Revocation (PDF)
Chargeback (PDF)
Check Recon (PDF)
Debit Card
Debit Card Replace (PDF)
Direct Deposit (PDF)
Hometech Signup
Loan Application
Open a New Account
Skip A Payment
Stop Payment (PDF)
Online Banking
Username:
Password:
Enroll
Open Account
Forgot password?
Get the app
×
Main Menu
Login / Signup
Our lobbies are reopened in a limited fashion! Before coming in, please be aware that you still need an appointment for some more intensive transactions. Read the full announcement here.
×
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us here at UBI Federal Credit Union. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose, and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purpose for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of your personal information is protected and maintained.
Quick Links
Apply for a Loan
Buy a Car
Find A Surcharge Free ATM
Get Insured
Make Loan Payment
Manage Credit Card Rewards
Open a New Account
Need More?
Contact Us
Locations
Privacy Policy
